// var questions = [
//     {

//         "question": "پایتخت ایران کدام شهر است؟",
//         "option1": "مشهد",
//         "option2": "کرمان",
//         "option3": "تهران",
//         "option4": "قم",
//         "answer": 3
//     },
//     {
        
//         "question": "انقلاب اسلامی ایران در چه سالی رخ داد؟",
//         "option1": "1360",
//         "option2": "1350",
//         "option3": "1345",
//         "option4": "1357",
//         "answer": 4

//     },
//     {
//         "question": "ستارخان در کدام شهر به دنیا آمده؟",
//         "option1": "تبریز",
//         "option2": "تهران",
//         "option3": "مشهد",
//         "option4": "بندر عباس",
//         "answer": 1
//     },
//     {
//         "question": "قله توچال در کدام استان می باشد؟",
//         "option1": "تبریز",
//         "option2": "تهران",
//         "option3": "مشهد",
//         "option4": "بندر عباس",
//         "answer": 2
//     },
//     {
//         "question": "کدام یک از گزینه های زیر برای طراحی صفحات سایت می باشد؟",
//         "option1": "php",
//         "option2": "java",
//         "option3": "c#",
//         "option4": "css",
//         "answer": 4
//     },
//     {
//         "question": "با کدام نوع تعریف متغییر ها دیگر نمیتوان محتوای آن را تغییر داد؟",
//         "option1": "let",
//         "option2": "var",
//         "option3": "const",
//         "option4": "int",
//         "answer": 3
//     },
//     {
//         "question": "سوهان مربوط به سوقات کدام شهر است؟",
//         "option1": "قم",
//         "option2": "مشهد",
//         "option3": "شیراز",
//         "option4": "تبریز",
//         "answer": 1
//     }
//     ,
//     {
//         "question": "گز سوقات کدام شهر است؟",
//         "option1": "کرج",
//         "option2": "کردستان",
//         "option3": "لرستان",
//         "option4": "اصفهان",
//         "answer": 4
//     },
//     {
//         "question": "استقلال چند بار قهرمان آسیا شده؟",
//         "option1": "2",
//         "option2": "1",
//         "option3": "0",
//         "option4": "5",
//         "answer": 1
//     },
//     {
//         "question": "سال 99 چه تیمی قهرمان لیگ شد؟",
//         "option1": "استقلال",
//         "option2": "تراکتور",
//         "option3": "پرسپولیس",
//         "option4": "پدیده",
//         "answer": 3
//     }
// ];


var questions = [
    {
        "question": "Web pages are designed using?",
        "option1" : "HTML",
        "option2": "CSS",
        "option3": "Javascript",
        "option4": "Jquery",
        "answer": 2
    }, 
    {
        "question": "Web pages are designed using?",
        "option1" : "HTML",
        "option2": "CSS",
        "option3": "Javascript",
        "option4": "Jquery",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "____ makes websites dynamic",
        "option1" : "CSS",
        "option2": "HTML",
        "option3": "Javascript",
        "option4": "Bootstrap",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What is HTML used for?",
        "option1" : "Skeleton of website",
        "option2": "Design a website",
        "option3": "Make website dynamic",
        "option4": "Database of a website",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which CSS property changes background color?", 
        "option1": "colour",
        "option2": "bgColor",
        "option3": "color",
        "option4": "background-color",
        "answer": 4
    }, 
    {
        "question": "Which selector selects all the elements in CSS?", 
        "option1": "*",
        "option2": "+",
        "option3": "$",
        "option4": "#",
        "answer": 1
    }, 
    {
        "question": "What is the value of a in a+=b where a=10 & b=5?", 
        "option1": "10",
        "option2": "5",
        "option3": "15",
        "option4": "20",
        "answer": 3
    }, 
    {
        "question": "What does 'document' denote in a javascript statement?", 
        "option1": "Javascript file",
        "option2": "Css file",
        "option3": "HTML page",
        "option4": "XML document",
        "answer": 3
    }, 
    {
        "question": "Which function is used to calculate an expression?", 
        "option1": "calculate()",
        "option2": "calc()",
        "option3": "evaluate()",
        "option4": "eval()",
        "answer": 4
    }, 
    {
        "question": "How do you call a function? ", 
        "option1": "call.function_name",
        "option2": "function_name.call",
        "option3": "call(function_name)",
        "option4": "function_name()",
        "answer": 4
    }, 
    {
        "question": "Javascript statements should end with a ... ", 
        "option1": "Comma",
        "option2": "Semicolon",
        "option3": "Period",
        "option4": "Exclamation",
        "answer": 2
    }		
    ];